{
    "subject": "resource/Empire_of_the_Ants_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/Work/runtime",
    "object": "89.0",
    "human_readable": "The runtime of the film Empire of the Ants is 89.0.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.5528302192687988,
            "question": "What is the runtime of Empire of the Ants in minutes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5513990521430969,
            "question": "What is the runtime of the film Empire of the Ants expressed in hours and minutes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4934558868408203,
            "question": "Is the film Empire of the Ants a short or a feature-length movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37481680512428284,
            "question": "Is Empire of the Ants a relatively long or short movie compared to others?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34808647632598877,
            "question": "How long is the film Empire of the Ants?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24041394889354706,
            "question": "If you start watching Empire of the Ants at 7:00 PM, what time will it end?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2221156805753708,
            "question": "If you have one hour and forty minutes, will you have enough time to watch Empire of the Ants?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22140362858772278,
            "question": "Approximately how long would it take to watch Empire of the Ants?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12463512271642685,
            "question": "What is the duration of Empire of the Ants expressed as a decimal number of hours?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12154559046030045,
            "question": "Could you comfortably fit Empire of the Ants into your afternoon plans?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The runtime of the film Empire of the Ants is 89.0.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8903_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the duration of Empire of the Ants expressed as a decimal number of hours?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8903_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Approximately how long would it take to watch Empire of the Ants?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8903_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you have one hour and forty minutes, will you have enough time to watch Empire of the Ants?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8903_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8903_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8903_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8903_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8903_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8903_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8903_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8903_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8903_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8903_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8903_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that the run time of \"Empire of the Ants\" is 89 minutes, which supports the given query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}